A Guide to the Peachy Family Papers, 1809-1883.
John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Library, Colonial Williamsburg Foundation
John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Library, Colonial Williamsburg
Peachy Family Papers, 1809-1816, 1809-1883.
John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Library, Colonial Williamsburg Foundation
MS 49.1
12 items.
Peachy family.
Administrative Information
Access
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift, 1949.
Alternative Form
Receipts also available on microfilm M-50.
Biographical/Historical Information
Thomas Griffin Peachy was born in 1734 to Samuel and Winifred Peachy. He married Elizabeth Gilliam in 1758. He died in Williamsburg in 1810.
Mary Mungo Cary Peachy was born in 1764 to Wilson Miles Cary and Sarah Peachy Cary. In 1787, she married Thomas Griffin Peachy's son William Samuel Peachy. She died in Williamsburg in 1836.
Scope and Content Information
Receipts given to Miles Selden by Thomas Griffin Peachy (1734-1810) and his daughter-in-law and administratrix Mary Munro Cary Peachy (d. 1836) of Williamsburg for payments toward the purchase of Flower de Hundred on the James River in Prince George County, Va. Also includes some miscellaneous materials relating to the Peachy family from the mid to late nineteenth century.
Arrangement
Chronologically arranged.
Index Terms
Family Names:
Peachey family.
Persons:
Peachy, Mary Munro Cary, d. 1836.; Peachy, Thomas Griffin, 1734-1810.; Selden, Miles, 1777- 1814.
Subjects:
Plantations--Virginia.
Geographical Names:
Flowerdew Hundred Plantation Site (Va.)
Genre and Form Terms:
Contracts--Viriginia--1809.; Receipts--Viriginia--19th century.
Contents List
- Receipt from T.G. Peachy to Miles Selden, Jr., 19 Feb 1809.
- Receipt from T. G. Peachy to Miles Selden, Jr., 11 August 1809.
- Contract between T. G. Peachy & Miles Selden, Jr. Agreement to secure to Blair's [Land], Deed 17 June 1815 executed, 23 December 1809.
- Receipt from Mary M. Peachy to Miles Selden Jr., 12 June 1810.
- Receipt from Mary M. Peachy to Miles Selden, 4 January 1811.
- Receipt from Robert Anderson for Mary M. Peachy to Miles Selden, Jr., 21 June 1811.
- Receipt from Robert Anderson for Mary M. Peachy to Miles Selden, Jr., 22 January 1812.
- Receipt from Mary M. Peachy to Fielding Lewis, 17 March 1813.
- Receipt from Mary M. Peachy to Miles Selden, 11 April 1814.
- Mrs. Peachy receipts to M. Selden for to purchase F. [Flower] d hundred, 11 April 1814.
- Memorandum on bond, 1815.
- Receipt from Mary M. Peachy to William Selden, 16 June 1816.
- Book fragment. Pages 375-382 of Aids to English Composition by Richard Parker Green. Published in Boston by Robert S. Davis in 1844, 1844.
- Check signed by Thomas Peachy, 15 Dec 1883.